https://www.aace.org/about/privacy/

Privacy Policy
AACE will never sell, rent, or exchange email or mailing addresses of its members, customers, and website users.
The Association for the Advancement of Computing in Education (AACE) is committed to protecting the privacy of its members, customers, and website users. AACE recognizes the interest of its members, customers, and website users in the confidentiality of their personal information. AACE only maintains personal information that is relevant to AACE activities and seeks to maintain accurate, complete, and timely information.
The security of personal information is important to AACE. AACE maintains all personal data with technical, administrative, and physical safeguards to protect against loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification, and improper disclosure. No computer system or information can ever be fully protected against every possible hazard. AACE provides reasonable and appropriate security controls to protect personal information against foreseeable hazards.
Email Policy
AACE will never sell, rent, or exchange email or mailing addresses of its members, customers, and website users.
AACE uses email addresses to send the following:
“Must Have” messages that help to service AACE members, customer, and website users including answers to questions; acknowledgments of the receipt of membership/subscription applications, renewal notices, and other orders.
Occasional “Member, Customer, & Website User Update” announcements about AACE services that we believe to be of some importance these groups. These announcements are usually brief, straightforward messages that contain pointers to online resources where readers can explore the information more fully.
Email messaging that is part of a program for which the user has registered (e.g. an AACE Digital Library Table of Contents Alert email).
Email distribution lists targeted at AACE groups (e.g. specific conference attendees or journal subscribers, etc.).
AACE created and supported email distribution lists such as the Eductech listserv have “unsubscribe” instructions.
Postal Mail Policy
AACE may use member and customer postal addresses to mail AACE related information that fall into categories #1 and #2 above.
EmailFacebookLinkedInRSSTwitterYouTube The Association for the Advancement of Computing in Education (AACE), founded in 1981, is an international, not-for-profit, educational organization with the mission of advancing Information Technology in Education and E-Learning research, development, learning, and its practical application. AACE serves the profession with international conferences, high quality publications, leading-edge Digital Library, Career Center, and other opportunities for professional growth.
About Contact
AACE Review
LearnTech U
AACE Connect
Information Request
Privacy Policy
Conferences EdMedia+Innovate Learning
Innovate Learning Summit
© 2020
Association for the Advancement of Computing in Education (AACE). All Rights Reserved.
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Reject Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
